These are Jack and Meg fights also known as The White Stripes their abandoned Detroit whose main gimmick is that they have no bass guitarist.
This is Steve McDonald of the veteran van Red Cross.
Steve hook White Stripes could use a bass player.
So he appointed himself.
He took the white striped latest album called white blood cells and re-recorded it laying a base crack down on every song then he released the results as MP3s on Red Cross has website.
He even made up a new album cover and title red blood cells ...
... McDonald began putting these copyrighted songs online without permission from the white stripes or their record label during Project he bumped into Jack White who gave him spoken a cent to continue.
It can be that easy when you skip the intermediaries collaboration across space and time creative co-authorship of people you've never met standing on the shoulders of your peers.
It's what the internet is all about.
It can be that easy when you skip the intermediaries, ...
... but wouldn't it be easier still not very many of us are liable to just bump into Jack White and get the green light isn't there an easier way for him to invite you and me to pick up a base as well.
Shouldn't we be able to if he doesn't mind easier still?
Enter one of the internet's most famous citizens face for me to the world over a public identity rivaled only by a handful of corporate Giants and Global Superstars.
The big copyright C.
Everyone knows what Big C stands for Big C means All Rights Reserved Big C means asked permission Big C protects copyright owners and notifies.
The rest of us of their ownership time was when you had to put big beyond anything the copyright or else it entered the public domain the commons of information where nothing is owned and all is permitted you had to put the world on notice to warn them that was being seized job and it was a useful one.